

BAO NGUYEN

Software Developer



Bao is a full-stack developer with a get-it-done attitude. Expertise in crafting web applications from scratch but also knowledge of cloud services.

Bao has three years of experience in web development ranging from E-commerce to industrial application. Also as a self-learn software developer, Bao is capable of working with new technology and out of his comfort zone.

CONTACT INFORMATION

- 24/06/1998
- baonguyendev98@gmail.com
- 046 800 0211
- http://baonguyendev.com/
- Tampere, Finland

EDUCATION

Energy And Environment Engineer

Tampere University Applied of Science (TAMK)

2016-2021

Bachelor of Engineer in Energy and Environment Engineer. Major in Circular Economy

SKILLS

• HIGHLIGHTED SKILLS:

React.js, TypeScript, C#, .Net.

FRONT-END DEVELOPMENT

React.js, TypeScript, React Query, Material UI, Tailwind

BACK-END DEVELOPMENT

Node JS (Express, Prisma, Nest) C#, and ASP.NET

DATABASE MANAGEMENT

MongoDB, PostgreSQL

• TESTING

Jest, Testing Library, superTest.

EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer

Integrify | January 2022--July 2022

- Focusing on front-end development with JavaScript, TypeScript, React.js, and Redux in addition to other technologies and concepts such as accessibility and animations.
- Building back-end for web-based applications with frameworks such as Node.js and Express.js..

Consultant Web Developer

Insta Oy August 2022--Now

 Built an industrial application from starch with a team of four senior developer. Technology in the application was React, .NET

RECENT PROJECTS

DEVOPS

Git, GitHub Actions, Docker, AWS

LANGUAGES

• English

Fluent

Finnish

Novice

Vietnamese

Native

Euro Jackpot Simulator

React.js, Redux, Material-UI, Reach Query, .NET, C#.

 Inspired by Veikkaus and a lot of reverse engineer, a full-stack application where users can play the Eurojackpot lottery and Lotto.

• Bao Nguyen's Portfolio

React.js, SASS, NPM

 A static site built with React and Tailwind CSS. The site is fully responsive, built to look clean and straight forward.

Netflix Clone

React.js, Public API, React Context

 An application built based on the design of the popular Netfix streaming application to showcase my abilities in frontend development. The application has functionalities and user interfaces similar to common streaming services, while the data is gathered using a public API.